https://ckslaw.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Cohelan Khoury & Singer Law Firm | San Diego, California
General
Cohelan Khoury & Singer employment law firm respects the privacy of every individual who visits our Web site. This privacy policy outlines how we will use the information you provide to us Cohelan Khoury & Singer. This statement also will instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared when you visit the Cohelan Khoury & Singer Web site.
Individually Identifiable Information
Cohelan Khoury & Singer will not collect any individually identifiable information about you such as your name, address, telephone number, or email address unless you provide it to us voluntarily.
If you do not want your individually identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have already submitted this information and would like us to remove it from our records, please contact us at the e-mail address or phone number listed at the bottom of this policy. We will use delete your information from our existing files
When you do provide us with individually identifiable information, we may use that information in the following ways unless stated otherwise: we may store and process it to better understand your case or potential case; we may use it to contact you; and we may use it in connection with employment litigation.
We have implemented reCAPTCHA on this website. The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.
Children
Cohelan Khoury & Singer has no intention of collecting any individually identifiable information such as name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address from individuals under the age of 13. If achild has provided us with individually identifiable information, that child’s parent or guardian should contact us at the e-mail address or phone number listed at the bottom of this policy if they would like this information deleted from our records.
Non-Individually Identifiable Information Collected Automatically
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not individually identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our site or advertisement.
Whom to Contact
If you have submitted individually identifiable information through Cohelan Khoury & Singer Web site and would like that information deleted from our records, please contact us at info@ck-lawfirm.com or call us at 888-808-8358. We will delete this information from our existing files.
Contact Us For More Information
FAQ
What is a class action lawsuit?
What to look for in an employment attorney
Most common mistakes made by employers
Legal Resources
CK&S in the media
CK&S published works
Checklist for labor lawyers
Useful law links
Contact Us For More Information
Name*
First
Last
Email*
Home Phone*Mobile PhoneEmployer or Company Case is Against(if this is an employment matter)Dates of Employment(if this is an employment matter)Address
Street Address
City
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
State
ZIP Code
MessageCommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Legal Resources
CK&S in the PressCK&S Published WorksChecklist for Labor LawyersFree 30-minute podcast on Brinker decisionUseful Law Links
FAQ
What is a class action?
What to look for in an Employment Lawyer
Ten Biggest Mistakes Made by Employers
Cohelan Khoury & Singer Class Action Attorneys
605 C Street, Suite 200 San Diego, California 92101-5305 phone: 888.808.8358 fax: 619.595.3000 Copyright © 2020 – Privacy Policy – Disclaimer
